<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Code Sydney</title>
  <id>http://codesydney.com/updates</id>
  <link href="http://codesydney.com/updates"/>
  <link href="http://codesydney.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-07-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Lucy Bain</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Getting started with Hipchat</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/hipcaht/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/hipcaht/</id>
    <published>2014-07-01T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-13T13:42:28+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Atlassian's &lt;a href="http://www.hipchat.com"&gt;HipChat&lt;/a&gt; now has free group chat - we'll use it to communicate between meetings. You can use this &lt;a href="https://www.hipchat.com/g3boxeZ8J"&gt;sign up link&lt;/a&gt; to join the Code Sydney group.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Use HipChat to ask questions, offer support, and stay in contact between meetings. Try not to give away the answer, but offer hints and tips - we're all here to learn!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  As always, leave a comment on this post or contact me if you have any problems getting started.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Four weeks to go</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/four-weeks/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/four-weeks/</id>
    <published>2014-06-09T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-09T17:25:26+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  We're starting in four weeks! Don't forget to go through the &lt;a href="http://codesydney.com/schedule/"&gt;prerequisites&lt;/a&gt; before then :)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  If you've decided not to participate in the study group, please let me know as there are people on the waitlist. Otherwise...
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  See you soon!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>So Many Peeps!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/closing-registration/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/closing-registration/</id>
    <published>2014-05-20T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-20T17:42:23+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Wow!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I've been absolutely blown away by Sydney's response to this study group. Over 30 people have registered, and we've still got over a month until the group starts. Thank you all!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  However, I'm a bit concerned about loosing the "group feeling" - that sense of accountability because we'll notice that you're missing. I also think 30 is plenty of people to be getting on with, it's certainly a lot bigger than my current study group. So from now on &lt;strong&gt;anyone who registers interest will be placed on a wait list.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  If you find that you won't be able to participate in the group, please let me know so someone else can take your spot. I'm sure they'll be very grateful for your consideration!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Start Date</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/start-date/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/start-date/</id>
    <published>2014-05-19T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-20T17:18:26+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Hi everyone!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Previously I wasn't sure about the exact start date, but I've talked with Atlassian since then. I'm now happy to announce that we're scheduled to start on &lt;strong&gt;July 7&lt;/strong&gt;! I've updated the &lt;a href="/schedule"&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt;, and included the public holidays we'll work around.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  A couple of you have been surprised that it's so far off. This really is the first Monday that's available - I'm currently running another study group for Python, which will be wrapping up in early June, once that's finished I'm heading off on vacation for the last week of June. I promise I'm not neglecting you!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  If you this means you can no longer participate in the group, please let me know (either through email or the comments).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  See you on July 7 - until then, don't forget about the prerequisites!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New Location!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/new-location/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/new-location/</id>
    <published>2014-05-14T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-14T13:15:17+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Thank you to everyone who has signed up - I've been amazed by the response so far! Yesterday we had our 20th registration of interest, more than I ever expected. I'm really excited to learn with all of you and see what we turn this study group into. I learned in my past study group that nothing will go quite as I expect - something that's already started with this one!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Since there have been so many interested people, I changed the location. My office wouldn't be able to handle 20 people (it could hardly take more than 12), and I'd hate to limit the study group based on my office size. So we will now meet at &lt;a href="https://www.google.com.au/maps/place/Atlassian/@-33.867265,151.206921,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x6b12ae393a03d8ff:0x8fead86f5e91b507"&gt;Atlassian!&lt;/a&gt; As you probably know, Atlassian hosts many meetups, and they were happy to accommodate ours.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  However, as I don't work at Atlassian, I will need a few Atlassian employees to let us up the elevators and to make sure everything gets cleaned up properly. If you are an Atlassian employee who is willing to help us in this way please contact me.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Thanks again to everyone who has signed up or spread the word!
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mark this RSS feed!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://codesydney.com/updates/save-this-space/"/>
    <id>http://codesydney.com/updates/save-this-space/</id>
    <published>2014-05-02T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-05T11:33:57+10:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  I'm not going to send out bulk emails to everyone unless it's absolutely required. You can subscribe to this RSS feed on your favourite reader, or use something like &lt;a href="http://ifttt.com"&gt;ifttt.com&lt;/a&gt; to get them emailed to you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  There are also comments enabled for each update. This serves as a kind of email thread as needed. Please let the group know any concerns/questions you have as we go through each week.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
